我知道我已经聊了一早上的鲍比
I know I've been talking about Bobby all morning,
但我喜欢鲍比还有一个原因是
but another thing I love about Bobby is,
他能搞懂我
he just gets me.
那他现在能来把你搞走吗
Can he come get you right now?
昨晚我给鲍比来了一点颈部激情
Last night, I gave Bobby a little neck action.
颈部激情  这么咸湿啊
Neck action? Oh, racy!
接下来呢  是不是要掀起你的裙子
What's next, you gonna lift up your skirt
露出你的膝盖给他看看
and show him your knees?
说不定哦
Maybe.
卡洛琳  等等我啊
Hey, Caroline, wait up!
掩护我  麦克斯
Hide me, Max.
鲍比还没看过我穿服务员制服的样子
Bobby hasn't seen me in my waitress uniform,
也没见过我右半边的脸
or my right profile.
一直用左侧示人真的很难
It hasn't been easy.
我们的制服哪里有问题
What is wrong with our uniform?
我叫它嘉丽
I call her Carrie
因为它身上也沾到了猪血
'cause she's got a little pig's blood on her
而且它无法被火焰烧毁
and she can't be destroyed by fire.
早安啊  小美人
Morning, beautiful.
我给你买了一杯玛奇朵
I got you a macchiato.
就得到如雷般鼓励的掌声
And a supportive round of applause
因为他们听到我是帮卡洛琳买
when I told them the name was Caroline.
鲍比  你太贴心了
Bobby, you are so sweet.
这加的是脱脂牛奶吧
This has skim milk, right?
无所谓啦
Oh, whatever!
你为什么要拿麦克斯当肉盾
Uh, why are you using Max as a human shield?
没关系啦  我习惯了
Oh, don't worry. I'm used to it.
我小时候我妈打劫餐厅时  也都用我当肉盾
It's how my mom robbed all those Carvels in the '90s.
我该走啦
I should get going.
所以...  来个团抱抱吗
So... group hug?
我还在想第三次约会该带你去哪
I'm still trying to figure out where to take you on our third date.
我希望这是个特别的约会
I want it to be special.
还有  我要么是压到了麦克斯的纽扣
Also, I'm either caught on Max's button
不然就是她有个又小又圆的鸡鸡
or she has a tiny, round penis.
建议你带你夹克去验性病
Might want to get that jacket tested.
再见啦
I'll see ya.
第三次约会吗
Third date?
你知道这代表啥意思  对吧
You know what that means, don't you?
如果以我上一个第三次为例
Going by my last third date,
他在第三次约会时出柜
he comes out of the closet,
然后我们仍持续约会了两年
and we still date for two years.
不是
No!
是代表更多颈部激情  只是是下面
It means more neck action, just lower.
你双腿间的那个"颈部"
Your between-legs neck.
麦克斯  你是个成年人了
You're an adult, Max.
那个叫疯狂吸尘器
It's called a noony-noo.
而且我还以为做爱是要到第十次约会
And I thought sex was on the tenth date,
在他不小心说出"我爱你"后才"做"
after he accidentally says, "I love you."
大家都知道第三次约会就代表打炮
Everybody knows the third date means sex.
而第四次约会是他莫名变得很有距离感
And the fourth date means he gets oddly distant
而且工作突然超忙
and crazy busy at work.
厄尔  今天[吊着]好吗
Hey, Earl, how's it hanging?
麦克斯  别说吊了  都垂到地上了
Lower than anyone will tell you, Max.
今早上厕所时  还以为有蛇跟我进来了
I thought a snake followed me into the bathroom this morning.
你们俩姑娘好吗
What's up with you girls?
卡洛琳要进行第三次约会啦
Oh, Caroline is going on a third date.
马上要有双腿之间的"颈部激情"啦
Oh, some between-legs neck action is on.
我真是压根没听说过你们这词
I am really not familiar with this phrase.
而且我也挺确定这个"第三约即炮"的规矩
And I'm pretty sure this whole "third date sex" rule
不是什么公认潜规则
isn't really a thing.
等到第三次约会才打炮啊
Waiting until the third date for sex?
你是修女吗
What are you, a nun?
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
好啦
Oh, all right.
别跟芭芭拉宝宝说话  我俩在吵架
Don't talk to Baby Barbara. We're in a fight.
她觉得情欲的《五十度》系列小说
She thought that the Fifty Shades book
比电影版好看
was better than the movie.
苏菲  你听说过大家应该在
Sophie, have you ever heard that you're supposed to
第三次约会时做爱的事吗
have sex on the third date?
不是修女才这么等吗
Oh, that's a nun thing, right?
我好庆幸我再也不需要面对这种事情
I am so glad I don't have to deal with this kind of stuff anymore.
我已经正式从炮界金盆洗洞
I am officially retired from sex.
不知道你们从新闻上听说了没
Not sure how many of you have heard the news,
也不知道你们读不读色情杂志《巨乳》
but not sure how many of you read "Juggs."
那杂志变得太严肃
It got too political.
所以我后来改读《大奶》杂志
That's why I turned to "Cans."
麦克斯  你说啥鬼话
Max, what are you talking about?
你怎么可以从炮界退休
You can't retire from sex.
那是你的特色啊  就像奇多零食
It's your thing, like Cheetos
还有对准别人内心脆弱之处痛击
or zeroing in on people's vulnerabilities.
啥  没听清  我被你鼻子上的痘痘搞分心了
What? Sorry, I was distracted by your nose pimple.
我只是觉得自己需要退圈远离江湖
I just feel like I need to get out of the game.
在炮界我没有遗憾  你随便问人
I had a good run, just ask
问任何人都能证明
literally anybody.
现在是你发光发热的时候了
But now it's your turn.
当一双腿合上时
Well, when one pair of legs closes,
世上会有另一双腿打开
another one opens.
我们波兰的奥普拉就这么说
Yeah, that's what Polish Oprah says.
而如果你跟她唱反调  你就会被吊死
And you get hanged if you disagree with her.
麦克斯  这事都不用天才...
Max, it doesn't take a genius...
虽然我在脸书做的智商测试说我是天才...
although my Facebook IQ test says I qualify as one...
但不用天才也知道你这炮界退休
to know that this whole retirement thing
还不是因为你跟兰迪分手的事
is about your breakup with Randy.
脸书也写了你有362个朋友
It also said you had 362 friends.
但我们都心知肚明你压根就没朋友
And we all know you barely have one.
我这事情跟兰迪没有任何关系
This has nothing to do with Randy.
我的性爱王座现在换你坐
My sex throne is yours now.
但我建议你垫块毛巾再坐
I would maybe put a towel down.
麦克斯  你不能这时候退出啊
Max, you can't get out of the game
我才刚回归炮界你就走
just when I'm getting back in.
我希望我们能一起做爱
I wanted us to have sex together.
先把你鼻子的痘给挤了  我们再谈
Well, clear up that nose zit, and we'll talk.
说鼻痘某个小鼻痘就来
Speaking of nose zits.
阿憨  麦克斯想从此不做爱
Han, Max is about to give up sex.
快告诉她不做爱的人生有多惨
Tell her how bad life is without it.
其实还挺丰富的呢
It's actually quite rich.
刚才我还在地滚球球场跟莫西摩说到...
I was just saying to Mossimo down at the boccie court...
谢谢  我已无需再言
Thank you! I rest my case.
我明天还要去上高尔夫球课呢
And tomorrow I'm taking golf lessons
多亏有我们的社区委员会组织
thanks to our community board.
另外也因为我的体重达不到练习
Apparently, I don't meet the weight minimum
以色列近身格斗术的最低标准
for Krav Maga.
这样吧  我跟你一起去
You know what? I'll go with you.
退休人士爱打高尔夫
Retired people love golf.
就像你们拉拉也都爱打
Just like you lesbians.
欢迎加入俱乐部[球杆]
Welcome to the club.
接下来一定会很好玩
This is gonna be fun!
我真心希望你知道你自己在干嘛
I hope to God you know what you're doing.
如果我要跟鲍比做爱  我得穿新内裤
If I am gonna have sex with Bobby, I need new underwear.
我现在这件上的破洞比《降临》剧情漏洞还多
My current pair has more holes than the plot of Arrival.
所以你来这里买吗
So you came here?
这里没有润滑油区
There's no lube aisle.
也没有任何假人在搞另一个假人
None of the mannequins are doing each other.
这间可是上等内衣店
This is a classy lingerie store,
不是二手婊服店
not Second-Hand Hose.
我被那店的人踢出来了
I got kicked out of there.
我把一盒可食用内裤吃了
I ate a pair of edible underwear
吃完还把盒子给放回架子上
and I put the box back on the shelf.
女士们  我是瑞塔  欢迎来到魅惑之艺
Ladies, I'm Rita. Welcome to the Art of Seduction,
一切的魅惑都始于...
where seduction begins with...
始于一杯龙舌兰
A shot of tequila
最后以一针盘尼西林治梅毒结尾
and ends with a shot of penicillin?
完全不是我要接的台词
Not what I was going to say at all.
不过有何能为两位效劳呢
What can I help you ladies with?
她马上要进行第三次约会了
Uh, she has a third date situation happening.
你有符合"重新大开幕"的内裤吗
Do you have anything that says "Grand Reopening"?
我希望风骚一点
I want to be naughty.
但是又容易觉得冷
But I get cold.
我看到了你们的鞋带专区  你们的内裤专区呢
I found your shoelace section, but where is the underwear?
那就是内裤
That is underwear,
而且你拿反了
and you're holding it backwards.
好吧  我现在看出来了
Oh, sure, I see it now.
我们去平价百货吧
Let's go to Target.
那你呢
And, uh, what about you?
有没有"第三次约会"啊
Any third dates coming up?
并没有呢
Actually, no.
我从炮界退休了
I am retired, sexually.
把门把上的袜子拿下  自己穿上了
Took the sock off the door and now I'm wearing it.
别闹了  麦克斯  我们都心知肚明
Come on, Max, we both know you're not
你不是真的退出炮界
really retired from sex.
我们是两个年轻性感尤物
We are two young, sexual beings.
这东西是该穿在哪里啊
Where are you supposed to wear this?
那是个手包
That's a purse.
如果我不是真退休
Uh, if I'm not retired,
那为什么拉里·弗林特会送我一只金表
then why did Larry Flynt send me a gold watch,
感谢我二十年来为国"服务"[子宫颈]
thanking me for my 20 years of cervix.
这件连体内衣如何
How about this teddy?
我只需要简单款
I just need simple underwear.
我想让我的"疯狂吸尘器"看起来美美哒
I want a nice presentation for my noony-noo.
其实你穿什么都无所谓
Look, it doesn't matter what you wear.
像你这样的身材  穿啥都很快会被脱掉
With a body like yours, it's not gonna be on long.
看到没  麦克斯  她喜欢我的身材
Ah, see, Max? She likes my body.
打从我退出江湖后  世人的口味就变了啊
Tastes have changed since I got out of the game.
这内裤很适合蹦跳时穿
And these panties are great to bounce in.
后面的荷边很能凸显你在做
The frills on the back really accentuate the twerk
摇摆琳达这招时的小电臀
when you're doing the Swingin' Linda.
琳达
Linda
想必是有着无数背部伤痛的奇女子
must have a bunch of back problems.
天啊  我需要做这招吗
Oh, my God. Do I have to do that?
当年美好的死鱼般躺下呢
Whatever happened to lying down?
现在那是男生做的工作了
That's a guy's job now.
我们这样的荡妇坏了你们的规矩
Skanks like us ruined that for you.
她没说错  不过呢
She's not wrong, but
我有在街角开舞娘班
I teach a burlesque class around the corner.
你应该来上上
You should come.
可以帮助你更亲密接触自己的身体
It can, uh, really help you get in touch with your body.
不用了  我已经与自己有非常亲密的"接触"了
Oh, it's okay, I'm already very in touch with my body.
是啊  她超"深入接触"
Oh, yeah. She's real in touch.
她废的电池够养活一个电池公司呢
This one's keeping Duracell in business.
麦克斯  我希望你也有从内衣店买了东西
Max, I wish you had gotten something at the lingerie store.
你骑上去的那个鞍好好看
That saddle looked really good under you.
被我骑都显好看
Most things do.
是曾被  我已经退休了
Did! I'm retired!
我们都知道你退休不了多久就会复出
We both know your retirement isn't gonna last.
就像是滚石乐队一样
You're like The Rolling Stones,
但你是用你自己的血来血偿
but with more of your own blood.
是吗
Really?
我看起来像是
Do I look like someone who will
这辈子还有炮打的人吗
ever have sex again?
撞衫你倒霉
Clothes jinx!
感觉像看到哈哈镜里的自己
It's like looking in a funhouse mirror.
但是少了哈哈
Without the fun.
我就过来告诉你明天下午茶是下午一点
I just came by to say our tee time is tomorrow at 1:00.
我们跟米奇与比尔四人行
We're in a foursome with Mitch and Bill.
无论如何千万别
Whatever you do, don't mention
在米奇面前提到海湾战争
the Gulf War in front of Mitch.
就算你要说"还弯"
Even when you say "Golf,"
也确保要字正腔圆
really hit the O.
麦克斯  别这样  你难道就不想
Max, come on, don't you want to unretire
再战江湖  来真正的"四人行"吗
and have a real foursome again?
就像你以前跟另外两人在我床上
Like you used to, on my bed,
而我试图在看书的那会
while I'm trying to read?
我喜欢现在这种无性生活
I like this sexless existence.
我不知道你一直在抱怨什么
I don't know what you've been complaining about.
而且我终于可以放飞自我
And besides, I can finally let myself go,
往卫生洞洞的天空飞去
hygenital-ly.
所以就因为你被兰迪伤了心
So because you got hurt by Randy,
你就再也不打算做爱了
you're never gonna have sex again?
不  我再也不做爱
No, I'm never having sex again
是因为我实在不知怎么脱掉这裤子
because I have no idea how to take off these pants.
鲍比  你怎么来了
Bobby! What are you doing here?
我等不及到明晚才见你
I couldn't wait till tomorrow night to see you.
我在一个基佬的婚礼捡到的  他们把这个丢掉
I got this from a gay wedding; they were throwing them out
因为这玫瑰不是他们想要的那种红
'cause they were the wrong shade of red.
天啊  这就像是《单身汉》真人秀一样
My God, this is just like The Bachelor.
不过少了节目上泡水后染性病的桥段
Except I'm not getting HPV from a lagoon.
别担心  麦克斯  我没忘了你
Hey, don't worry, Max. I didn't forget you.
我的刮刮乐
My scratch-offs!
新郎们婚礼不撒米  而是撒这个
The grooms were throwing those out instead of rice.
好吧  我要发个朋友圈
Well, that's going on my Pinterest.
明晚就是我们隆重的第三次约会啦
So tomorrow night's our big third date.
大家也都是这么跟我说
That's what people keep telling me.
我准备了非常特别的东西呢
I've got something real special planned.
很有异国风情
It's exotic.
我想你肯定会大为赞叹
I think you'll be very impressed.
我肯定会的
Oh, I'm sure I will be,
不过过程得需要一点时间
but it takes me a little while,
而且我是属于"不出声"赞叹那种
and I'm quiet when I am.
别担心
Hey, don't worry.
你就放心把一切交给我
I'll do all the work.
我也会出一点点力啦
Well, I'll pitch in a little.
肯定会让你"大"吃一惊
It's gonna be big.
明晚见
See you tomorrow night.
又大又外来种[异国风]  什么玩意  鹦鹉吗
Big and exotic? What is it, a parrot?
如果是鸡尾鹦鹉  那我愿意重回炮界
If it's a cockatiel, then I'm back in the game.
至少我有超性感的内衣裤防身
At least I have that really sexy underwear.
姑娘们  我刚听到"内衣裤"这个词
Hey, girls. I heard the word "underwear."
有个老太婆把她的内裤落这里了
Some old lady left her panties back here.
奥列格  那不是老太婆的内裤
Oleg, those aren't old lady panties,
那是我的
they're mine.
你是要送给一位老太婆吗
Are you bringing them to an old lady?
还是要送这位先生的夫人
Perhaps this gentleman's wife?
奥列格  这内裤很性感好吗
Oleg, these are sexy.
你凭什么觉得自己是内裤专家
What makes you a panty expert?
除了生鸡勃勃州颁发给我的官方老淫贼牌照
Besides my official license plate from the state of arousal
和操你大学颁发的学位证之外
and my degree from Idu U?
没了
Nothing.
我得去上舞娘课才行
I have to go to that burlesque class.
我不知道  你应该看看
I don't know, you should see if
操你大学有没有夜校可以上
they have night classes at Idu U.
你穿着打高尔夫球的衣服要怎么跳舞
How are you gonna dance in those golf clothes?
那你穿得像个放荡贵宾犬又怎么跳舞
How are you gonna dance looking like a slutty poodle?
我们先来选道具吧
Let's just pick out our props.
我一早上都在说服自己接受这门课
I've been sanitizing for this all morning.
我有次被人扔车后备箱投湖  就穿着这玩意
I was once dropped into a lake in a trunk just like this.
那些码头暴徒肯定想不到我还活着
Those dock goons did not expect to see this gal again.
羽毛披肩
Ooh, feather boa!
我好久没穿过带羽毛的东西了
I haven't worn something with feathers
上次还是因为有鸽子飞进我们的电扇
since that pigeon flew into our fan.
这是我从家带过来的
I brought this from home.
是我第三次坐嘉年华邮轮的纪念品
I got it on my third Carnival Cruise.
你就让给她吧
Oh, let her have it!
这姑娘要进行第三次约会了
Girl's going on a third date.
哇  那相当于基佬的第一次约会
Ooh, that's a gay first date.
我第一次约会地点是霍尔与奥兹的音乐会
My first date was a Hall & Oates concert.
没错  我老了
Yes, I'm old.
欢迎各位同学
Welcome, everyone!
我们开始上课了  一起来变性感吧
Let's get started. It's time to get sexy!
没错  根据我的《好色客》手表
Yep, according to my "Hustler" watch,
现在时刻  11点69式
It's 11:69.
不对啊  感觉现在没那么晚
Can't be right. Feels earlier.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我吼着追了你们三条街  让你们等等我
I was screaming at you for three blocks to wait up.
结果发现人行道上的卡洛琳原来是路灯柱
But then sidewalk Caroline turned out to be a lamppost.
苏菲  你来这里干嘛
Sophie, what are you doing here?
我在餐厅看见了板子上的名片
Well, I saw the card on the board in the diner,
而且我想给我和奥列格的性生活增添点趣味
and I wanted to spice up Oleg and my sex life.
我是说  我们有好几周没冲着
Yeah, I mean, we haven't done it in front of
《今日秀》的玻璃窗做爱了
The Today Show window in weeks.
我真不敢相信主持人在吐时
I can't believe they didn't cut away
电视台居然没有把画面切掉
when Matt Lauer threw up.
我上一次做爱时  人们还能
Last time I did it, you could
把可卡因放在随身行李中
still bring cocaine in your carry-on.
在这门课上  我们要试着深入
In this class, we are going to go deep
并释放我们体内的性感女神
and unleash our sexual goddesses.
我体内的女神让我被军队踢出来了
Mine got me kicked out of the army.
他们问  我说了
They asked; I told.
开始跳舞吧
Let's dive in!
大家到椅子后面
Everybody get behind your chairs.
我先给你们演示一遍  然后再分解动作
I'm gonna show you the routine and then I'll break it down.
我好兴奋啊
I'm so excited.
我即将失控
I'm about to lose control
我想我喜欢这种感觉
and I think I like it!
♪ 今天不是我生日 ♪
♪ It's not even my birthday ♪
♪ 不过他想舔掉蛋糕的奶油 ♪
♪ But he want to lick the icing off ♪
♪ 我知道你想用最赤裸的方式大快朵颐 ♪
♪ I know you want it in the worst way ♪
♪ 你已经迫不及待要吹灭蜡烛 ♪
♪ Can't wait to blow my candles out ♪
♪ 他想要吃我的蛋糕 ♪
♪ He want that cake, cake, cake, cake, cake, cake, cake ♪
♪ 今天不是我生日 ♪
♪ It's not even my birthday but...♪
算了  我做不做爱都无所谓
You know what? I don't need to have sex.
我还是跟你去打高尔夫吧
I'll just play golf with you.
我打高尔夫是为了甩开我老婆
Uh, I play golf to get away from my wife.
我好累
Well, I'm exhausted.
我得打个盹
I need a nap.
通常我一跳完就会流失大部分学生
After I dance is when we usually lose most of the class.
在我教大家真正的舞步前
Now, before I teach you the actual moves,
我想让你们去感受自己的身体
I want you to just feel your body
并释放它
and let it go.
谁想来试试
Who wants to give it a shot?
我来  我来
Oh, I do! I do!
我要在"舞娘课"上"舞臀"
I want to put the "ass" in "class."
苏菲  如果我想看你的臀
Sophie, if I wanted to see your ass,
我直接早起看《今日秀》就行了
I'd get up early and watch The Today Show.
我卡住了
I'm stuck, but you know what?
我对天发誓  我一定能跳好
I swear to God, I can make it work.
我都不太敢问了
I'm, uh, scared to ask this,
可谁想下一个来
but who's next?
我能试试吗
Is it okay if I try?
那动作是我唯一能跟上的了
That was probably the only act I could follow.
加油  妹子
Go, girl!
我不记得身上这条裤子会让人"硬起来"啊
I didn't think these pants came with a boner.
我完全不知道是怎么回事
I don't know where that came from.
人们常说旋律会感染人
You know how they say the rhythm is gonna get you?
果然是真的
It got me!
我得走了
Well, I gotta go.
屁股过了两点的位置了
It's ass past two.
你的屁股休想从我这过
Well, your ass isn't getting past me.
我现在能跳这舞后
Ooh, now that I can dance,
个性也变霸气了
I'm sassy too.
卖弄风骚  卖骚
Let's tease. And tease.
装纯情  人家没有卖骚啦
Did I do that? Did I do that?
继续卖骚  卖骚
And tease. And tease.
真豪放  我的确在卖骚
I did do that. I did do that.
前后动  扭屁股
And pump. And grind.
抛媚眼
Wink.
我就是这样来到这个国家的
That's how I got to this country.
不过我当时还一边在划船
Except I was also rowing.
你为什么不跟着跳
Why aren't you participating?
我上周也这么跟那穿运动裤的男人说
Like I told that guy in sweatpants last week,
你不能光坐在那里看
you can't just sit here and watch.
我跟那家伙不一样
Well, unlike that guy,
卖弄风骚对我来说已是过去式了
my days of sexy moves are behind me.
从现在开始  我唯一会亲密接触的"球"
From now on, the only balls I'll be smacking
在高尔夫球场上
are on the golf course.
你真的要放弃自己的本性
You're really gonna give up on who you are
就因为兰迪吗
because of Randy?
她经历了一场分手
She went through a breakup,
就发誓要戒掉性爱
and she swore off sex,
我有点担心她连除臭剂都戒了
and I'm worried maybe deodorant.
这个呢...
Oh, yeah, that's
可能是我包包里的那包脏尿布
probably my bag of dirty diapers in my purse.
放在宝宝纪念册里作为留念嘛
I'm putting them in my baby book.
这就是这门课的意义所在
This is what this class is all about.
将所有痛苦与愤怒
Taking all that pain and anger
变成性感的舞步
and making it sexy.
我还以为这门课能把我的屁股练到能鼓掌
I thought this was about making my booty clap.
会练到的  加文
We'll get there, Gavin.
跟我说说兰迪这个人
So tell me about this guy, Randy.
没什么好说的
Uh, there's nothing to say.
这事跟他无关
It's not about him.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
他让你心情消沉吗
Did he bring you down low?
当然  沉到谷"底"
Oh, sure he did. Real low.
让你爽翻天吗
Shake you up?
爽到升"天"
All shook up.
别在老娘面前晃你的没肉屁股
Hey, get your ass out of my face, razor hips.
他可曾让你转过身子
Did he spin you around
然后从你的生活中溜走吗
and slide right out of your life?
就像油腻的麦乐鸡
Like a greasy McNugget!
让我看看你的宝贝鸡
Show me that nugget.
我也想  可这裤子脱不下来
I would, but I can't take these pants off.
麦克斯  拜托
Max, come on.
你不能让一次痛苦经历毁掉一切
You can't let one bad experience ruin everything.
我如果像你  我也用不了我们的浴室地垫
Otherwise, I'd never use our bath mat again.
那玩意莫名其妙烫脚
It's hot for no reason.
对啊  我都违章停车了  快跳一个啦
Yeah, I'm double parked! Come on, dance already!
好吧  如果这样我能赶紧离开的话
Fine! If it will get me out of here.
没错  释放出来
That's right, get it out there!
我撞撞撞  我扭扭扭
Bump, bump! Grind, grind!
鸭鸭鹅  抛媚眼
Duck, duck, goose! Wink!
跳起来  宝贝  跳起来
Ooh, yeah, bounce, baby, bounce!
天啊  太真实了
God, this is so real!
好吧  我承认
Okay! Fine!
或许我的确是因为兰迪而封闭自我
Maybe I am shut down 'cause of Randy.
瞧  你需要说出来  感觉好点了吗
See, you needed to get that out. Do you feel better?
不好  我脸上插了木头倒刺
No, I got a splinter in my face.
不好意思  我要失陪了
Well, if you'll excuse me,
我得去上高尔夫球课了
I have a golf lesson to get to.
晃晃屁屁  各位拜拜
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, Max out.
她不会告诉别人
She won't tell anyone
那些舞步是在这里学的吧
she learned those moves here, will she?
我是最棒的  对吧
I was the best, right?
因为我很在乎名次
Because it matters to me.
快把你们的老公老婆藏起来
Hide your husbands. Hide your wives.
麦克斯回归了
Max is back.
我要挥别退休生涯
I'm out of retirement
和这条裤子  我会尽快脱掉的
and these pants, as soon as I can get them off.
天啊  你是跟阿憨上床了吗
Oh, my God, you slept with Han?
让我先找出你当初给我
Let me find that machete you gave me
说如果你俩睡了  就拿出来砍死你的刀
in case this ever happened.
不  她睡的是我们的高尔夫球手
No, she slept with our golf pro.
我又一次拿着推杆被人扔下不管
Once again, I was left holding my putter.
是的  我重出江湖了
Yep, I'm back,
我头上的草汁渍可以作证
and I have the grass stains on my head to prove it.
瞧  那堂课帮了所有人
See? That class helped everyone.
除了苏菲  我走的时候
Except Sophie... by the time I left,
身上又多卡住了三把椅子
she had three more chairs on her.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
做好准备
Brace yourself.
苏菲性趣十足
Sophie got sexified.
额滴神
Oh, my God.
这舞步和那性感的脖圈
Between those moves and that sexy neck brace,
我的小心脏快要承受不了
it's too much for me to take.
这就是我跟精灵说
This is what I get for telling that genie
我想活到100岁的下场
I wanted to live to be 100.
苏菲
Sophie...
能去冷库那里碰面吗
could I see you in the walk-in freezer?
如果你不介意  能不能加上瘸腿舞步
And if you don't mind, could you add a limp?
你知道最性感的部分是什么吗
You know what the sexiest thing about it is?
瘸腿是真的
The limp is real.
兄弟
Hey, buddy.
你好呀
What's going on, man?
鲍比
Bobby!
我刚午餐休息
Hey, I was just on my lunch break,
想说过来看你  结果只看见一个头
thought I'd stop by and almost see you.
跟你约会很开心
Well, it was nice dating you.
这是我的工作制服  我知道它...
This is my uniform. I know, it's...
正  真的超正
Hot. Really, really hot.
你看起来像是一根性感的铅笔
You look like a sexy pencil.
可我专门买了超性感
But I bought all this really sexy,
还很多拉链的内衣  等着第三次约会时穿
very zipper-heavy underwear to wear on our third date.
为什么第三次约会时我会看见你的内衣
Why would I see your underwear on our third date?
那不是应该在第十次的时候吗
Doesn't that happen on the tenth?
我也是这么说的
That's what I said!
你们这群禽兽
You people are animals!
但你上次不是说
But what was all that talk about
我们的约会会又大又异国风吗
our date being big and exotic?
我是打算带你去那家摩洛哥餐厅
I was gonna take you to this Moroccan place.
那里没有椅子  我们得坐枕头上
They don't have chairs. We sit on pillows.
那的确很异国风[奇特]
That is exotic.
你们俩最好先停一停  别着急滚床单
You might want to hold off on the sex.
因为你俩没准是兄妹
You two might be related.